{
    "gradesList": [
      {
        "name": "Grade 10",
        "subjectList": [
          {
            "name": "Science",
            "chapterList": [
              {
                "name": "Matter",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": "What is matter?",
                    "answer": "Anything which occupies space and has a mass is ccalled matter."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "Name three common states of matter.",
                    "answer": "Solid, Liquid, Gas"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          },
  {
            "name": "English",
            "chapterList": [
              {
                "name": "Tense",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": "Was John reading the book last night? Name the tense.",
                    "answer": "Past Progressive"
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "Will they have won the match? Name the tense.",
                    "answer": "Future Perfect"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "name": "Verb",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": " I ___ watching TV when Paul and Simon arrived.",
                    "answer": "was"
                  },
                  {
                    "question": "Do you think he ___ what I said?",
                    "answer": "understood"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Grade 11",
        "subjectList": [
          {
            "name": "Science",
            "chapterList": [
              {
                "name": "Electric Charge",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": "What is charge?",
                    "answer": "Electric Charge is that physical property of matter due to which the other matter experience a force when matters are placed in electromagnetic field."
                  },
                  {
                    "question": " How much positive and negative charge is there in a cup of water?",
                    "answer": "The number of molecules in one cup of water is (250/18) × 6.02 × 1023"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          },
  {
            "name": "Mathematics",
            "chapterList": [
              {
                "name": "Equation of line",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": "What is the slope of x=0?",
                    "answer": "Infinite"
                  },
                  {
                    "question": " What is the slope of y=0?",
                    "answer": "Zero"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Grade 12",
        "subjectList": [
          {
            "name": "Social Studies",
            "chapterList": [
              {
                "name": "Rulers of USA",
                "questionList": [
                  {
                    "question": "Who controlled the colony of New York before the English?",
                    "answer": "The Dutch"
                  },
                  {
                    "question": " Who was the founder of New York and New Jersey?",
                    "answer": "The Duke of York"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }